欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
鳕鱼角 前情提要
Previously on Hightown
对我来说 戒毒的感觉挺好的
For me, sobriety's been  good.
今后我会继续和州警合作
Im working with State Police- - moving on up.
现在事情有点不一样了
Things are a little bit different now.
我自由了
I'm a free man.
豪尔赫 欢迎回家
Jorge, welcome home.
谢谢你帮我搞定那个条子
Thanks for sucking that cop's dick.
你和线人搞上了
You fraternized with a CI.
你被停职了
You're suspended.
我不适合正常生活 都他妈快折磨死我了
I'm not cut out for this normal life- - fucking killing me.
你会用上纽约那边的关系吗
Will you be using the New York connect?
供货是我负责的
Supply is my responsibility
-搭档吗  -搭档
Partners? - Partners.
欢迎来到翡翠城 兄弟
Welcome to Emerald City, brother.
我是珍妮尔 你的理疗师
Im Janelle, your physical therapist.
你他妈开枪打我
You fucking shot me!
他得彻底消失 就好像从来没存在过一样
He needs to disappear like he never fucking existed.
豪尔赫死了
Jorge's dead.
-什么  -这是他的应急包
- What? - This is his go bag.
他不会丢下这个包走人的
He would never leave without it.
我需要你
I need you.
夏梅恩现在正在纽约重新上货
Charmaine's in New York right now re- upping.
你他妈怎么知道的
How the fuck do you know that?
-蕾妮告诉我的  -我们抓到夏麦尼了
Renee told me. - We got Charmaine.
我是来要回我的工作的 我可以把弗兰基·奎瓦斯抓来给你
I want my job back. I can bring you Frankie Cuevas.
等文书流程走完 你就算正式回来了
As soon as the paper clears, you're back.
我正在着手打造纽约那边的关系
I'm setting up on the New York connect.
我是回来做警探的 艾伦
I'm coming back as sergeant, Alan,
你要滚蛋了
and you're going to Body Side.
凶杀组 我是桑蒂勒
Homicide, this is Saintille.
他听到传言说 有牙买加清洁女工埋了一具尸体
He heard a rumor Jamaican cleaning ladies buried a body.
豪尔赫低估了她 看看他的下场
Jorge underestimated her and look what happened to him.
我都没想到会这样
Even I didn't see that coming.
你现在有什么要和我说的吗
Is there anything you need to tell me right now?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
有人给你付了保释金
Your bail's been paid.
你准备好去见我叔叔了吗
So you read y to meet my uncle?
纽约之王
King of New York?
奥西托向你问好
Osito said "what's up"!
我要上厕所
I need a bathroom.
别跑 别跑 夏梅恩
Stop! Stop, Charmainel
他们一直在搜索林子 但毫无发现
They've been searching the woods and nothing.
针对此事 会有一次调查
There's going to be an investigation.
-她太冲动了  -操
She has impulse issues. Fuck-
我要换搭档
I will be requesting a new partner.
你该喝一杯
You deserve a drink.
我全都搞砸了 操
I fucked everything up! Fuck!
我不会卖东西给条子的
I ain't gonna sell nothing to a cop.
让我进去行吗
Just let me in.
请进吧 警官
Come on in, Officer.
我想了很多关于你的事
♪Ithought a lot of things About you ♪
♪ Ithought a lot of things About you ♪
我睡不着 只想着你
♪ Istayed awake ♪ust thinking about you ♪
但现在我离开了
♪But now I'm away ♪
♪ But now I'm away ♪
你必须得留下
♪ You had to stay ♪
明天属于我
♪ Tomorrow's a day of mine ♪
不再有你
♪ That you won't be in ♪
♪That you won't be in ♪
我也想说我只是在享受生活
♪ I tried to say I was just having fun ♪
但我知道你就是对的那个
♪ But I really knew That you were the one ♪
♪But I really knew That you were the one ♪
但我知道你就是对的那个
♪ But I really knew That you were the one ♪
现在我走了
♪ And now that I'm gone ♪
♪And now that I'm gone ♪
我知道我错了
♪ I see I was wrong ♪
我早该明白的
♪I should have known AlI along ♪
♪I should have known All along ♪
时间会证明一切
♪ That time would tell ♪
离开你一周时间
♪A week without you ♪
我应该要忘记
♪ I should forget ♪
♪I should forget ♪
离开你两周时间
♪ Two weeks without you ♪
我还在想着你说的话
♪ And Im still thinking about The things that you said ♪
♪And I'm still thinking about The things that you said ♪
我还在想着你说的话
♪ And I'm still thinking about The things that you said ♪
假期 依然可爱
♪ Vacation ♪ust another love- in ♪
假期希望你能爱我
♪ Vacation I hope you love me ♪
假期 你能念着我吗
♪ Vacation Would you think of me? ♪
我觉得我要不告而别
I think I'll leave Without saying goodbye
♪ I think I'll leave Without saying goodbye ♪
我觉得我要不告而别
我觉得你知道为什么
♪ I think that you know The reason why ♪
要是我留下呢
♪ What if I was to stay? ♪
事情是否会不一样
♪ Would things turn out Some other way? ♪
反正我也不会知道了
♪ I'll never know anyway ♪
比比谁跑得快
Race you in!
爸妈说在他们醒之前
Mom and Dad said don't go swimming
不要去游泳
before they wake up.
-我不在乎 我要去游  -等等我
Icon't care. fm going in. Wait for mel
我的天 我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我们得去叫爸爸
We should get Dad.
我觉得我们该去看看
I think we should go look
别 别这么干
Don't. Dont do that
别这么干
Don't do that!
干什么
What the fuck?
我这是在哪儿
Ugh. Where am I?
海滩上
The beach.
七大洋汽车旅馆旁边
By the Seven Seas Motel.
你们有看到我手机或者钱包吗
You guys seen my- my phone or wallet anywhere?
好吧
AlI right.
祝你们玩得开心
Have a good one.
记得防暑
Stay cool.
发狂吧
♪Go berserk ♪
♪ Go berserk ♪
看着这些婊子劳动 看看这些婊子劳动
♪ Watch these bitches work Watch these bitches work♪
看着这些婊子劳动 看着这些婊子劳动
♪ Watch these bitches work Watch these bitches work ♪
钞票从天而降
♪ Money fallin From the ceiling ♪
落在地上 落在地上
♪To the dirt, to the dir♪
她心情低落 所以嗑了点药
♪' She was tunrt down So she popped her a Perc♪
♪She was tunrt down So she popped her a Perc...♪
不 兄弟 不不不
Nah, bro. Nah, nah, nah, nah.
大联盟里是能睡到好女人 但现在不行了
You get better pussy in the majors but not more.
小联盟3A的女人那才叫够劲儿
There's mad hos in the Triple A.
-这女的人呢  -我不知道
Where is this chick? - I don't know.
每次我真要找她
She's all over the fucking place
就找不见了
till I actually want to see her.
扔下几张钞票 她就听你指挥
♪ Threw some Franklins Then direct her like Kirk ♪'
看 那儿呢
Look. There.
她有双D 她有双D
♪ She got double Ds She got double Ds ♪
她和杜克·杜斯睡
♪'And she fuck With Duke Deuce ♪
双D 双D
♪ Them double Ds double Ds ♪
我和脱衣舞娘玩闹在一起
♪ Ifuck with stripper hos And they fuck with me ♪
玩闹在一起
♪And they fuck with me ♪
过来
Come here.
你们想干嘛
Now, what you boys want?
救命
Hey! Help!
米西 救民
Missy! Help!
-操  -快啊 米西
- Fuck. - Hurry, Missy!
米西
Missy!
-她要跑了  -我他妈知道啊
She's getting away! - I fucking know.
米西 让我进去
Missy, let me inl
走走走走
Go, go, go, go!
-靠  -走走走走
Shit. Go, go, go, go!
靠
Shit.
你想离开
♪ You want to go ♪
但我觉得你该留下
♪But think You should stay here ♪
弯腰碰不到脚趾 但我可以是救世主
♪'Can't touch my toes But I can be a savior ♪
我知道之前就有人这么说过
♪'Iknow That it's been said before ♪
但我会再大声说一次
♪But I'll say it again Louder, for sure ♪
我做过保证 我也可能搞砸了
♪ I made a promise I might've messed up ♪
我说过我会在 但我会打扮一下
♪ Isaid Id be there But I'll play dress- up ♪
我知道如果你能握住我的手
♪ I know if you just hold My hand ♪
那你就会理解了
♪Then you'll understand ♪
因为我只想要你的声音
♪Cause all I wanted Was your voice ♪
你见过我的车吗 邦妮
Have you seen my car, Bunny?
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
等等
Oh, wait.
你能帮我打个滴滴吗
Actually, you think you could call me a Lyft?
我们知道
♪ And we know ♪
你想松手
♪ You want to let go ♪
12月我们逮捕了
After we arrested Charmaine Grasa
夏梅恩·格拉萨之后
back in December,
我们从她手机里调取了记录
we were able to pull tolls from her cell phone.
你是说在你抓住夏梅恩·格拉萨
You mean after you arrested Charmaine Grasa
但在几天后把她弄丢之前吧
but then before you lost her a few days later.
是的 马克森警长
Yes, Mlajor Markson.
就像我刚才说的 通话记录显示
As I was saying, phone records identified
拉尔菲·帕西斯是她在纽约的门路
Ralphie Patsis as her New York connect.
我们认为拉尔菲同时也在供货给
We believe Ralphie is also supplying
伊曼纽尔·德尔加多 也就是奥西托
to Emmanuel Delgado, AKA Osito.
但真正的目标是拉尔菲的叔叔 乔治·帕西斯
But the real target is Ralphie's uncle, George Patsis.
能不能快进到有意思的部分
Can we please fast- forward to the good part?
我只想知道什么时候能抓人
I just want to know when I can make arrests.
很快了 长官 马上就可以了
Oh, we're close, sir. We're right there.
多快
How close?
这是联邦案子 所以不光由我们决定
Well, it's a federal case, so it's not only our call,
但我们已经和烟酒火器管理局合作了
but we've partnered with the ATF,
现在国税局也想加入
and the IRS wants in now.
-是吗  -这个混蛋
Yeah? This asshole- -
他每个月都从中国
he's bringing in dozens of containers
运来几十个集装箱
from China every month.
记录显示他赚8万5
On paper he makes 85G,
但他的房子值六百万
but his house is worth $6 million.
所以 你自己算吧 是吧
So you know, go fucking figure, right?
所以真的很快了 警长
So we're close, Major.
好 继续
AlI right. Carry on.
从现在开始 每周
Let's start having these briefings weekly
都开这样的简报会 行吧
from now on, huh?
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
奎尼奥内斯探员
Agent Quinones.
感谢你的加入
Thank you for joining us.
-抱歉  -赶紧滚去工作
Sorry. - Get the fuck to work.
你拿回你的工作了 警探
You got your job back, Sergeant.
那就好好干
Do it
关门
Close the door.
我现在问你一个问题
I'm gonna ask you one question right now.
你他妈认真的吗 杰基
Are you fucking serious, Jackie?
我知道 抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
第一天重回一线就迟到
You're gonna be late for your first day off desk duty?
而且还是警长简报会
During a debrief with the Major?
不会有下次了 我保证
It won't happen again. I promise.
只是 我的车被偷了
It's just...my car was stolen.
什么 在普罗文斯镇吗
What? In P- Town?
-真的吗  -我感觉是的
For real? - Yeah. I mean, I think so.
你感觉是 你感觉你的车被偷了
You think so? You think your car was stolen?
还是你忘记自己把车停哪儿了
Or did you forget where you parked it?
你认真的吗
Really, dude?
我隔天就要做尿检
I get pee tested, like, every other day.
我要真嗨上了
If I was partying,
你绝对是第一个知道的人
you would literally be the first person to know.
我必须得问
I had to ask.
好吗要我重新开始吗 那我重新开始
Okay, want me to start over? I'm gonna start over.
欢迎回到一线 奎尼奥内斯探员
Welcome back to the field, Agent Quinones.
你不用继续待在办公室这个炼狱
You are off desk purgatory,
我赦免你所有的罪孽 孩子
and I absolve you of your sins, my child.
看吧 没事了
See? It's good.
我不会让你失望的 老大
Yeah, I won't let you down, boss.
对夏梅恩的搜索有新发现了吗
Anything new on the search for Charmaine?
除非她做点蠢事
U. S. Marshals aren't gonna find her
否则法警是抓不到她的
unless she does something stupid.
她不会的 操
Yeah, she won't. Fuck.
所以 你今天要我干什么活
So, like, what do you got me doing for work today?
我需要你去波士顿送张传票
I need you to go up to Boston to deliver a subpoena.
可以 没问题
Cool, cool.
靠
Shit.
我没车啊
No car.
我帮你调辆警车来
I’ll pull a trooper off the road for you.
为戴茜小姐开车
Fucking Driving Miss Daisy over here.
谢了
Thanks.
我的毒品摊子大赚特赚
♪I been getting money In the trap house, hustlin'♪
高质量二手车
我的毒品摊子大赚特赚
♪ I been getting money In the trap house, hustlin'♪
高质量二手车
你想买就能买无需多说
♪If you want to get it you Can get it, no discussion ♪
你想买就能买 无需多说
♪If you want to get it, you Can get it, no discussion ♪
玩我的钱
♪Playin'with my money...♪
这V8发动机可是好东西
Now, you got to appreciate that big V8 engine.
警察用这款车是有理由的
There's a reason why police use this car.
我喜欢 但买下来之前
I ike it, but I got to run it by my wife
我得问过我老婆
before I pull the trigger.
别忘记跟她说
Just don't forget to mention
这是同等级里安全性最高的了
it's got the highest safety rating in its class.
到处乱搞
♪Mess around and I do ♪
好
Yeah.
祸从口出
♪ Loose lips sink ships ♪
我没听到你说什么
♪ I ain't heard What you said ♪
戴上面罩 戴上面罩
♪ Mask up, mask up ♪
现在你看不到我的脸了
♪No, you can't see my face ♪
戴上面罩 戴上面罩
♪ Mask up, mask up ♪
拉尔菲 怎么样
Ralphie, what's up?
没什么 你怎么了
Nothing. What's up with you?
我马上派人去你那里
Gonna send somebody down your way,
拿那个地方的东西
pick up those things from the spot.
是吗 什么时候
Oh, yeah? What time?
-8点  -好 行
Eight o'clock Okay, yeah.
没事的 告诉我你想要什么
It's okay. Just tell me what you want.
你要什么我都给
I will give you anything you want.
告诉我你想要什么
Just tell me what it is.
好吗
Okay? -
没事 没事
It's okay. It's okay.
她想尝口我的华夫饼吗
Does she want a bite of my waffle?
不 她还不能吃那个 宝贝
No, she can't have that yet, baby.
把它放下 去洗手 好吗
Put it down. Go wash your hands, okay?
嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh, shh, shh.
没事了 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
-没事的  -嗨 你还好吗
It's okay. - Oh, hey. How you doing?
她就一直哭
She won't stop crying. -
好了 给我吧
Okay, give her to me.
给我 把她给我
Give her to me. Give her to me.
过来吧
Come here.
斯嘉丽 好了
Oh, Scarlet Yeah.
好了 我的宝贝女儿怎么样了
Yeah, how's my little baby girl?
怎么了
Yeah, how's- Oh.
瞧瞧她
Oh, look at that.
这下谁更有本事了
Who's got the magic touch, huh?
-你的乳头怎么样了  -糟透了
Hey, how are your nipples? Horrible.
行吧 我给你买了你要的乳霜
AlI right, well I got you that cream you asked for.
要我帮你涂吗
Want me to rub it in there for you?
你想得美
Yeah. No.
六个礼拜不能做爱
No sex for six weeks.
而且我现在恶心死了 所以
Besides, I am disgusting, so...
不
No. - Mm- hmm.
不 你是我的美丽宝贝
No, you're my beautiful baby.
好点吗
Hmm. How's that? - Mmm.
-太棒了  -是吗
So amazing. - Yeah?
是啊
Yeah. -
又来了
Oh, right there.
不 不 别停
No. No, don't stop.
我得走了 宝贝 抱歉
Got to go, baby. I'm sorry.
-不  -抱歉 宝贝
No. I'm sorry, baby.
不 你才刚来
No, you- you just got here.
是 我知道 但有工作
Yeah, I- I know, but it's work.
-不  -是工作
No. It's work.
不 我这一个月都几乎没出过门
No, I've barely left the house in a month.
我很想你
I miss you.
好吗 我想念和成年人的对话
Okay, I miss talking to grown- ups.
那个妈妈互助小组呢
What about that mom support group thing?
你知道吧 你可以去那里
Mm. You know, you could go there.
交点新朋友
You coulcl make some new friends.
我能跟一群家庭主妇聊什么
What do I have to talk about with a bunch of housewives?
我不知道
I don't know.
你现在不是家庭主妇吗
I mean, aren't you a housewife now?
拜 斯嘉丽 拜
Bye, Scarlet. Bye.
我听说
Well, I heard
这傻逼现在要带屎袋了
this motherfucker got a shit bag now.
你有什么要说的吗
You got something to say?
我说
I said.
我听说你现在要带屎袋了
I heard you got a shit bag now.
你他妈给我滚 傻逼
Just get the fuck out of my face, pendejo.
我本来是要了结他的
Yo, I was gonna finish this motherfucker off.
但我是真可怜他
But I dead- ass feel sorry for this nigga.
你俩知道规矩的 隔开30英尺远
You two know the rules 30 feet apart.
没事啊
No stress.
我只是打个招呼
I was just saying hey.
赶紧走开 屎袋
Move it along, shit bag.
看来我们对弗兰基的谋杀案起诉
Seems our murder case against Frankie rests
完全取决于拉蒙·桑切斯 也就是排骨的证词上了
entirely upon the testimony of Ramon Sanchez AKA Chuleta?
你们凶杀组就拿出这么点成果吗
Is that all the Homicide Unit has come up with?
那排骨在秦被杀的时候确实在现场
Well, Chuleta was present during the murder of Chin
而且秦和休斯顿的坟也是他挖的
and dug graves for Chin and Houston.
他是个很有力的目击者
He's a strong witness.
那他是怎么说豪尔赫·奎瓦斯被杀一案的
Well, what does he say about the murder of Jorge Cuevas?
他说他毫不知情
Well, he says he has no knowledge of it.
但弗兰基肯定也不会到处
- But it's not like Frankie
吹嘘说自己杀了表哥吧
would run around bragging about killing his cousin.
你解释下 我有什么理由不撤回豪尔赫一案的起诉
Give me one reason not to withdraw the Jorge charges.
我给你两个理由
I'll give you two.
查尼斯·贝利和卡米娜·沃森
Chanise Bailly and Carmina Watson,
都是牙买加人
both of Jamaica.
我收到消息 她们帮忙埋了豪尔赫
I got a tip that they helped bury Jorge,
大概是在弗兰基的指示下
presumably on the order of Frankie.
但她们在那之后不久就消失回牙买加了
But they disappeared back to Jamaica right after.
目前为止 牙买加政府
And thus far, the Jamaican authorities
还没能找到她们
have been unable to find them.
但或许 如果地方检察官办公室
But maybe if the District Attorney's Office
可以 你懂吧 给点压力
could, you know, put some pressure
给到国务院 我们就可以
on the State Department, we could- -
我更希望在美国领土上
I'd prefer to find a witness
找到目击者
within the continental United States.
继续找 桑蒂勒
Keep looking, Saintille.
鳕鱼角跨机构缉毒组指挥中心
航海路118号凶杀案
老天
Oh, boy.
我真是操了
Fuck me.
小萨尔
Lil Sal.
是我们第一次抓到她持毒 给她留了案底 对吧
We're her first possession charge, right?
还记得吗 我们在她妈家门口抓的她
Remember that? We popped her in front of her mother's house.
你他妈在这儿干什么
Fuck you doing here?
怎么了 六个月来第一起谋杀
What? First murder in six months- -
这我怎么会错过呢
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
第一起谋杀
First murder?
我一周要出三次吸毒过量案的现场
I've been going to, like, three overdoses a week,
多亏了那些假冒伪劣毒品
thanks to these knockoff pills going around.
对比之下冰毒都显得像阿得拉似的了
They're pressing meth that look like Adderall, huh?
-芬太尼像阿普唑仑似的  -我知道
- Fentanyls look like Xannies. - Hey, I know.
我知道 我在办了
I know. I'm working on it.
这纽约的案子可难搞了 行吗
This New York case is a bitch, all right?
所以你准备找你兄弟奥西托问问吗
So you gonna call your boy Osito about this?
我兄弟 你他妈什么意思
My boy? What the fuck you mean?
我就是说 是你跟他谈的交易嘛
I just mean you're the one who cut him the deal, right?
那是为了抓你兄弟弗兰基
Putting your boy Frankie away,
之前他能出来纯粹是因为你这混蛋
who was only out because of your ass.
你他妈
Who the fuck are you- -
你们能不能暂时放下你们这该死的自尊
Can you put your fucking dicks away for five minutes?
尊重一下死者好吗
Show a little respect for the deceased, huh?
-我们只是在聊案子而已  -然后呢
Just talking about the case. - And?
小萨尔是个独立承包商
Well, Lil Sal here is an independent contractor.
她这是在弗劳利的地盘上
So she's in Frawley territory.
我觉得该查查欧文·弗劳利
I'd look at Owen Frawley.
欧文·弗劳利是他妈谁啊
Who the fuck's Owen Frawley?
冉冉升起的毒贩新星 奥西托给他供货
Up- and- coming dealer. Osito supplies for him.
肖恩·弗劳利的侄子
Shane Frawley's nephew.
肖恩·弗劳利 南波士顿那个吗
Shane Frawley? From Southie?
不只是南波士顿
Not just of Southie.
他在全州范围内有30处不同的生意
Got 30 different businesses across the state.
刚买下了28号公路那边那家微型赛车场
Just bought that Go- Kart place out on 28.
我们觉得现在流通的假货背后就是他侄子
We think his nephew is behind all the pressings going around.
我听着是条调查路子
Sounds like an avenue of investigation to me.
米勒上
Miller's up.
你做副手 好吧
You take second lead, all right?
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
操
Fuck.
你有什么具体目标吗
You looking for anything in particular?
我们这里所有认证过的二手车保修都不错的哦
We got a sweet warranty on all our certified pre- owned.
瞧瞧你
Hey, look at you.
多气派 多漂亮啊
You're looking nice, spiffy.
小萨尔·兰戈尔德死了
Uh, Lil Sal Rangold turned up dead.
你知道可能是谁干的吗
Any idea who might have did it?
哪个萨尔
Sal who? O
或许是弗劳利家的小的 欧文
Maybe it's that, uh, Frawley kid, Owen.
没听过这人
Never heard of him.
你没听说过这个
You never heard of the guy
把你的毒品做成假药的家伙吗
who's pressing your dope into fake pills?
没有 但你这话听着挺离谱的
No, but that sounds fucked up.
这样吧
Well, I tell you what,
我可能知道些你想聊的事儿
I might have something you want to talk about.
弗兰基的审判马上就要到了
Frankie's trial is coming up.
我们利益应该是一致的吧 想把他留在里面
Thinking we got a common interest- - keeping him inside.
所以 你在豪尔赫·奎瓦斯被杀一案上知道些什么线索吗
So you got, um, any information on the murder of Jorge Cuevas?
不重要了 我不告密的
Doesn't matter. I ain't a snitch.
鬼扯
Bullshit.
弗兰基上次被抓就是因为你
You're the reason why Frankie got arrested the last time.
不 我对他没意见
Nah. I got no problem with the man.
真的吗
Really?
所以你的狱友才捅了他一刀吗
Is that why your cellmate stuck metal in his gut?
监狱会让人做出一些疯狂的事情
Prison makes you do crazy things.
还好我出来了
Good thing I got out.
你是保释出来的
You got out on bail.
保释不等于自由了
And bail is not out.
你还得去受审
Still got a trial hanging over your head.
我能花钱请到最好的律师 O
Hey, well, I got the best lawyer money can buy.
我的审讯延后了
My trial's pushed.
但你不能一直拖下去
But you can't push it forever.
那就走着瞧吧
We'll see.
但现在 我是个自由人
But right now I'm a free man.
所以 除非你要买车 否则我没什么好跟你说的了
So, unless you need a car, I got nothing for you.
回头见
Talk soon.
那是干什么
What was that about?
欧文对一个女的下手了
Owen put some lead in old girl.
我去处理
I'ma go see about it.
她就一直
She was all,
米西 米西 让我进去
Missy, Missy let me inl"
米西就 操 滚 傻逼
And Missy was like, "Fuck, no, bitch.
你马上要被人爆头了
You about to get your head hollowed in. "
好了 我热完身了
AlI right, man, I'm loose.
帮我搞定
Bro, set me up.
欧文
Owen,
Owen.
我们得聊聊
We need to talk
聊什么
About what?
一垒安打
Aah! Base hit.
关于小萨尔
About Lil Sal.
谁
Who?
-三垒安打  -那事儿不妙
Stand- up triple. That shit's not a good look.
有个条子来找我
I had a cop come see me.
要是有贪心的婊子
Yeah, well, some greedy bitch
在我的地盘上卖货 然后被干掉了
is selling on my block and gets got,
那不是自找的吗
she probably had it coming, right?
我跟你说过那些假药的事儿了
And I told you about those pressies.
那玩意儿太引人注目了
That shit brings too much heat.
瘾君子就是瘾君子
Fucking junkie's gonna do
他就是要嗑 你能怎么办呢
what a fucking junkie's gonna do, man.
我他妈又不是卫生局局长
Who am I, the Surgeon fucking General?
越过森林了 傻逼
Over the Green Monster, bitch!
我早就知道能行的
Should have called that one, kid.
早就知道能行的
Should have called that one.
逻是有何贵干
Well, to what do I owe this pleasure?
这是有何贵干
你侄子在招惹是非
Your nephew's bringing some heat.
-是吗  -是啊
Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
出了起谋杀
There was a murder.
谋杀对所有人来说都不好
Murders are bad for all of us.
欧文不听话
And Owen don't listen.
他是个好孩子 而且能挣钱
He's a good kid, and he earns.
这小鬼需要管束
The boy needs limits.
要么你管 不然我来管
Now, either you handle this, or I will.
我从来都没有孩子 至少我不知道有
I never had kids- not that I know of.
我唯一的姐妹几年前死了
My only sister passed a few years back.
-就是欧文的妈  -那又他妈的怎么了
She's Owen's mom. - So the fuck what?
要我为你伤心吗
You want me to feel bad for you?
不 我要你在威胁我家人之前
No, I want you to think twice before threatening
仔细考虑一下
my family again.
你听懂了吗
You hear me?
只是生意而已
It's just business.
要是他想继续跟我做生意
If he wants to keep doing business with me,
那就得低调点
he needs to chill out.
你想继续挣大钱
You want to keep getting that good pack,
就给我关好这事儿
you need to make this right.
我会跟他聊聊的
I'll speak to him.
所以呢
So?
所以 其实是排骨的证词
So, it's really Chuleta's testimony
让你的处境不太妙
that makes your situation untenable.
那我们就找到排骨 然后我们
Then we find Chuleta, and we get- -
拜托 我求你别说完这句话
Please, I'm begging you not to finish that sentence.
然而 假设来说
However, hypothetically speaking,
如果你想要一个更有创意的辩护方针
if you wanted a more creative defense,
那还是有选择的
there are options.
不过需要花钱
But they cost money.
多少钱
How much?
我觉得差不多10万吧
I'd say 100 grand would get you
就能有你想要的创意了
just the right amount of creativity.
这我五千就能搞定
I could get it done for five.
必须要给最高价
Payments need to be made at the highest level.
这需要时间的
It will take time.
我可以先去着手办事
Now, I can get that process started
你来凑钱
while you find the money.
但州政府冻结了你的资产
But the state has frozen your assets.
还有豪尔赫的应急包
There's still Jorge's go bag.
我看过证据开示文件了 就不存在这玩意儿
I've been through the discovery files- - it doesn't exist.
我被抓那晚 那个包就在俱乐部里
It was at the club the night I got arrested
里头有快30万现金 还有货
with almost 300K in cash and product.
你给我证明那群混蛋偷了那个包
So prove those motherfuckers stole it
推翻我这个案子
and get my case thrown out.
在警方渎职问题上
It takes a lot to surprise me
我已经见得太多了
in regards to police malfeasance.
但这个案子里
But in this case,
我不觉得是他们偷了你的钱
I'd be very surprised if they stole your money.
要是他们没偷 那就是别人偷了
Well, if they didn't do it, someone else did.
谁
Who?
那个贱人
That fucking puta.
嗨 我是蕾妮
Hi, I'm Renee,
我很高兴成为一个新手妈妈
and I love being a new mom.
我很喜欢和一个
I love being locked inside
在侵蚀我身体的小孩
with a baby
一起被关在家里
who is literally eating my body.
我也很喜欢这种不睡觉的生活
And I love not sleeping.
我是想说
I mean.
为了孩子 要我杀人都可以 但
I would kill for my kids. It's- -
但斯嘉丽的爸爸一直不回家
It's just Scarlet's dad is never home.
小弗兰基的爸爸不在
Frankie Jr. s dad is away...
从来都不在
like, forever.
也不是说我想念以前的生活
And, I mean, it's not like I miss my old life exactly.
只是
It's just
我不知道
I don't know.
钱 女人 钱 女人
♪Money, pussy Money, pussy ♪
钱 女人 钱 女人 钱 女人
♪Money, pussy, money, pussy Money, pussy ♪
亲爱女人 亲爱女人
♪Honey pussy, honey pussy ♪
亲爱女人
♪ Honey pussy ♪
亲爱女人 亲爱女人 亲爱女人
♪Honey pussy, honey pussy Honey pussy ♪
我有那甜蜜
♪ I got that honey...♪
蕾妮
Renee?
我的天 你怎么来了
Oh, my God. What are you doing here?
我就是 路过来看看
Uh, I just, uh, came for a quick visit.
不打扰吧
I hope that's cool.
当然了 这是
Yeah. Is this
-是啊  -小斯嘉丽吗
Yeah. - Baby Scarlet?
嗨
Oh, hi.
嗨 小斯嘉丽
Hi, baby Scarlet. -
我在INS上见过你
I've seen you on Insta,
但你真人更可爱哦
but you're even cuter in person.
她太完美了吧
She's so perfect.
是啊
Yeah, it's, uh...
确实很棒
it's amazing.
希望是吧 因为我也怀上了
Well, I hope so because I'm having one, too.
我的天 恭喜
Oh, my God. Congrats.
一切都发生得很快 但我认识了一个很好的人
Yeah, it happened really fast, but I met this great guy.
我们决定要一个孩子
We decided to go for it.
他跟我的前男友很不一样
He's really different from my ex.
太棒了 我真的很为你开心
That's amazing. I'm really happy for you.
所以你现在是经理了吗
So are you the manager now?
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
在弗兰基那事儿出了之后
After everything went down with- with Frankie and all that,
应该说是只剩我了吧
I was sort of the last man standing.
挺好的
That's great.
-谢了  -是啊
Thanks. Yeah.
那我给你拿杯可乐吧
So, like, can I get you a Coke or something?
这样 你能不能给我份工作
Actually, could you get me a job?
真的吗
Really?
我是说
I mean, uh...
我不是
I- I didn't.
我不是想说这个 但
I didn't really mean to say that, but, um...
但 是的 我可以
but, yeah, I mean, I could.
我可以做的助理经理
I could be your assistant manager.
我 我已经有一个了
Oh. I- I already have one.
好吧 好
Okay, yeah, um.
但是这样的
But the thing is, um...
我得离开家里
I need to get out of my house,
我得自己赚钱
and I need to make my own money,
我得为自己做点什么
and I need to do something for myself.
而这里
And- and this is.
这是我做过的唯一一份真的工作 所以
this is the only real job I've ever had, so, um...
我什么都可以做
I'll do anything.
不好意思
Excuse me,
但塔菲又冲了她那大棉条进马桶
but Taffy flushed one of her big- ass tampons again,
现在马桶堵了
and the toilet overflowed.
操你妈 你怎么知道是我
Fuck you, bitch. How do you know it was me?
好 我来处理
Okay. I'll deal with it.
我的天
My God.
唐娜 听着
Donna. Hey.
我可以负责管姑娘
I could manage the girls.
是吧 我知道怎么处理脱衣舞娘闹事
You know, I- I know how to handle stripper drama.
而且 我会排班 还有
And- and I know how to make a schedule, and.
我可以当这里的舍监
You know, I could be the house mom.
拜托
Please.
我真的很需要这个
I need this.
我把你和我说的话 再和你说一遍
I'm gonna tell you what you told me.
这地方烂透了 它会侵蚀你的灵魂
This place sucks, and it'll eat your soul.
但我真的很讨厌脱衣舞娘闹事 所以
But I fucking hate stripper drama, so...
欢迎来到泽维尔俱乐部
welcome to Xavier's.
嗨 我从波士顿回来了 你需要什么吗
Hey, back from Boston. You need anything?
不 没事了 你可以走了
No, no, you're good. You can go.
那个 尿检女士来了
Hey, uh, the pee test lady's here.
好 行 我去做了它
Yeah, okay. Uh, cool. Yeah, I'll go do that.
明早见
See you bright and early tomorrow.
你知道规矩的 探员
You know the drill, Agent.
知道 谢了
Yep. Thanks.
好了 你过了
Okay, you're good.
晚安
Have a good night.
嗨 罗恩
Yo, Ron.
Yo, Ron!
怎么了
Oh, wassup?
所以 就
Yeah, so, like,
我就想问下 我们昨晚是不是一起玩儿了
I was wonderin', did we hang out last night?
是的吧
We did, right?
因为我找不到我的车还有我的手机了
Cause I can't find my car or my phone.
啥都找不到了
...or anything.
杰基 上周五之后我就没见过你了
Jackie, I haven't seen you since Friday.
老天 这是你记得的最后一件事吗
Jesus Christ, this is the last thing you remember?
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
只是 记忆有点模糊
It's just- it's just a little fuzzy.
我记得我们在沙丘营地玩儿来着
Uh, I remember we were hanging out at Camp Dune.
对 然后你想从个家伙身上弄可卡因
Yeah, and then you wanted to score coke off some guy,
还要我开车送你
and you wanted me to drive you.
那时候我就赶紧跑路了
That's when I got the hell out of there.
那你他妈就该送我的
You should've fuckin' driven me, then.
不然我就不会惹上这麻烦了
I wouldn't be in this shit.
那现在这不是好了吗
Well, we're here now.
咱去喝一杯
Let's go get a drink.
我们可以邀请埃德
We can invite Ed.
你知道吧 他真的很想你
You know, he really misses you.
不 不能叫埃德 我现在没空应付他
No no Ed. Icannot deal with him right now.
但我确实需要人送我一程
But I do need a ride.
有什么可以帮到你的吗
Can I help you?
老天
Oh, Jesus.
-怎么 你认识我吗  -她什么都记不得了
- What? You know me? - She can't remember shit.
昏迷两天
It's a two- day blackout.
我只是想找到我的车
I'm just trying to find my car.
你知道些什么吗
You got any information about that or...?
我都不记得自己什么时候来过
I mean, I don't even know when I was here.
你和另一个女孩是周六入住的
You and the other girl checked in Saturday.
什么女孩
What girl?
就 你的女性朋友
You know, your lady friend.
你有照片之类的吗
You got a picture or something?
我还真有
Yeah, actually.
上日班的齐克 他可会剪辑了
Zeke on day shift, uh, he knows all about editing,
所以他做了个 叫什么来着
so he made a- - what do you call it? - -
视频混剪
a supercut.
我到处给人看呢
I've been showing it around.
我们要完蛋
We need to get fucked up!
这是你们入住的时候
Mm, there's you guys dhecking in.
我和蠢货在一起
"I'm with stupid. "
闭嘴
Shut up.
那天我们收到了一堆噪音投诉
We got a bunch of fuckin' noise complaints that day.
抱歉
Sorry.
好了 好了 谢谢你
Oh, okay. All right, thank you.
大家都懂了 别放了
I think we got it. Stop playing.
听着 你知道这女孩是谁吗
Look, do you know who the girl is?
不知道 你们是用你的名字登记的
Nope, you checked in under your name.
那是我开车来的吗 她把车开走了吗
Well, did I drive my car here? Did she take it?
我只想知道到底发生了什么
I just need to know what happened.
你觉得我的工作就是坐这儿记笔记吗
Do you think I sit around taking notes?
但清洁工在你们的房间里找到了这些东西
But the maid did find this stuff in your room.
谢谢你 操 谢谢你
Thank you. Fuck, thank you.
谢谢你 郎达
Thank you, Ronda.
谢谢你
Thank you.
整挺好
Good on you.
靠
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit
朋友 她是真辣啊
Oh, dude, she's hot.
老兄 这不是重点
Man, that's not the point.
操 怎么这破事儿老是找上我
Fuck, why does this shit always happen to me?
是啊 我也不知道
Yeah, I got no idea.
肯定是此生最大的谜题之一吧
It must be one of life's great mysteries, huh?
听着 好了
Hey, all right.
没事了 没事的
Okay. You're okay.
来吧 我请你喝一杯
Come on, let me buy you a drink.
要说我有没有想过能在爱情岛上
I mean, did I think I was gonna find somebody
找到像你这样的人
like you on Love Island? -
那我确实没有想过
Mm- mm. No, I didn't.
-我也一样的 就
...same way. It's like- - Hey.
他们人都去哪儿了
Where's everybody?
是个奇迹
It's a miracle.
他们同时睡着了
They're both asleep at the same time.
来看爱情岛
- Come watch Love Island.
你的妈妈互助小组怎么样了
What, um, what happened at the mom group thing?
挺好的
It was good.
那位小组长
Yeah, the, um, leader girl
说自我时间是很重要的
said that me time is really important,
所以我让我妈妈明天
so I asked my mom to watch the baby
来看几个小时孩子
for a few hours tomorrow.
如果你不介意的话
if that's okay.
当然了
Yeah, of course it is.
我只是希望你能开心
Hey, I just want you to be happy.
好吗
Okay?
所以今天工作如何 珍妮尔
So how was work today, Janelle?
在理疗室破坏了哪个可怜虫的灵魂了吗
You break some poor dude's spirit in the PT room?
我不是破坏人的 我是帮助人变强壮的
I don't break people. I strengthen them.
那你是这么对我的吗
Mm, is that what you did to me?
是 还不止呢
Among other things.
这样真的很不错
This is nice.
是啊
Yeah.
听着 我 我很抱歉
Hey, I'm- - I'm sorry.
我得接个电话
I got to take this.
很快
Real quick.
喂 怎么了
Yo, what's up?
老兄 你能不能跟你的人说一声
Hey, man. Can you tell your runner
我可能要晚个30分钟
I'ma be late 30 minutes?
你还要带东西去别的地方吗
And you still got to take her to the other place?
不不不 就在我身上
Nah, nah. I got the shit with me, bro.
搞什么 你带着货乱跑吗
What the fuck? You ridin'dirty?
是 我有好多事要办
Yeah, I had mad errands to run,
而且我现在9点得到城里
and I got to be in the city by, like, nine now,
但就这么一次
but it's just this one time.
最好是
It better be.
靠
Shit.
操
Fuck.
朋友 这么看吧 你睡了太多女人
Dude, look at it this way- - you get so much pussy,
都记不住了
you can't even remember it all.
可这都不好玩了
It's just not fun anymore.
什么 女人吗
What, pussy?
一切都是
Everything.
我的生活 我的工作
My life, my job.
你他妈这是怎么了
What the fuck happened?
周五你还在兴奋终于不用坐办公室了
On Friday, you were so stoked to be getting off of desk duty.
不 我确实是 但
No, I mean, I am, but
自从我们抓了弗兰基
ever since we put Frankie away...
我就失去大目标了
I don't have a white whale.
我们还有个纽约的大案子
I mean, we got this big case in New York,
但不一样了
but it's just not the same.
抓掉弗兰基也没什么用
And putting Frankie away didn't help.
那些被他杀的人 又不可能活过来了
I mean, the people that he killed, they're still dead.
我就没有大目标
I don't have a white whale.
只有普通目标
I just got regular whales.
你真是太蠢了
You're so stupid.
这是工作
It's work.
所以他们才会给你发工资
That's why they pay you to do it.
那我就是希望受到激励 真是不好意思了
Well, sorry for wanting to be inspired.
还有 自从莱斯莉被调走
Also, since Leslie got transferred- -
调走
Transferred?
她不是因为你们俩丢了那女的
Didn't she get demoted down to Highway Patrol
被贬去做高速巡警了吗
cause the two of yous lost that chick?
老天
- - Jesus, man.
你是想让我更难过吗
What, are you trying to make me feel worse?
我的天
Oh, my God.
你去哪儿
Hey, where you going?
谢谢你
Thank you.
当当
Boom.
这是什么
What is this?
氰化物
Cyanide.
我受不了你抱怨了
Can't listen to you whine anymore.
摇头丸啦
It's fuckin' Molly.
哪个蠢货给你卖摇头丸
What idiot sold you Molly?
你他妈看上去就像个缉毒警
You look like a fucking narc.
那你就是个缉毒警
Well, you literally are a narc,
也没见你忍着啊 赶紧嗑吧
and it's never stopped you, so just fucking take it.
你们搞什么
You guys, what the freak?
我是阿布鲁佐
Abruzzo.
我是纽约警局的迪亚斯警探
Hey, this is Detective Diaz, NYPD.
我们刚刚逮捕了一个叫拉尔菲·帕西斯的小孩
Just picked up a kid, Ralphie Patsis,
他肇事逃逸
for a hit- and- run.
我查他的时候 跳了你的名字
When I ran him, your name came up.
想着通知你一下 我们在他车上
Thought you'd want to know, we found three kilos
找到了三公斤海洛因
of heroin in his car.
不
Oh, no.
把他放了
kick him loose.
什么
What?
那小鬼很重要 我欠你个人情
I got a lot riding on that kid. I'll owe you one.
鬼扯吧 还他妈欠个人情
Get the fuck out of here with"I'll owe you one. "
我给你打电话都是你走运了
You're lucky I even called you.
操
- Fuck!
-怎么了  -我得走了
- What's happening? - I got to go.
-什么  -真的很抱歉
- What? - I'm so sorry.
真的很抱歉 宝贝 我得走了
I'm so sorry, baby. I got to go.
警长
Major?
拜托
Come on.
-阿布鲁佐 搞什么  -抱歉
Abruzzo, what the fuck? - I'm sorry.
我给你打过电话的
- I tried calling. -
但听着 如果我们现在不做决定
But listen, our entire case is about to go down the drain
那整个案子马上就要完蛋了
unless we make a decision right now.
做什么决定
Yeah, a decision about what?
拉尔菲·帕西斯刚刚带着三公斤毒品被抓了
Ralphie Patsis just got picked up with three kilos of dope.
他叔叔一得知他被抓
The moment his uncle finds out he's in custody,
就会被惊动
he's gonna get spooked,
会毁掉整个行动的
he's gonna blow up the whole operation.
好了 所以你想要什么
AlI right, so what do you want?
我要去抓他
I want to go get him.
就现在 今晚
Right now, tonight. -
我需要逮捕令
I need an arrest warrant.
我需要搜查他家的搜查令
I need a warrant to search his residence.
听着 我们已经抓到他逃税漏税的把柄了 好吗
Listen, we already got him on the tax stuff, okay?
我们可以把拉尔菲那三公斤毒品联系到他身上
And we can tie the three keys from Ralphie to him.
我们还有其他线索
We have other threads going.
如果我们能进去他家
If we can get in his residence,
就能找到证据把一切联系起来
we can find stuff to tie everything together.
是 这有可能行 但也有可能不行
Yeah, that- that might work. It might not.
你也有可能因为这次糟糕的逮捕
You might just blow your wad on a bad arrest
直接毁掉六个月的工作成果
and then fuck six months of work.
但如果我们不去
But if we don't go,
这六个月的工作就肯定完蛋
we definitely fuck six months of work.
瞥长 我现在走 日出前就能到
Major, I leave right now, I'm there before sunrise.
行 好 行吧
Yeah, okay. Fine.
我去联系地方检察官给你申请逮捕令
I'lI call the AUSA, get you a warrant.
谢谢你 谢谢你 我去通知组里人
Thank you. Thank you. I'm gonna alert the team.
顶上像假发一样
♪ On top like a toupee, top ♪
可能会给我一个新的宝贝
♪Might find me A new bae, you ♪
给我柠檬味美汁源
♪ Give me lemons Make Minute Maid, yum ♪
婊子 我是碧昂丝
♪Bitch, I'm Beyonce ♪
那婊子说什么
♪ What that bitch say? ♪
婊子 我是碧昂丝
♪Bitch, I'm Beyonce ♪
操
Oh, fuck.
雷
我们今晚就要逮捕帕西斯
凌晨5点长岛高速公路53号出口集合
操
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck!
我得去纽约做事了
I got to go to New York for work!
杰基 你正嗨着呢
Jackie, you're rolling balls.
我知道
I know!
我知道 但我们要有大动作了
I know, but something big's going down,
如果我不去 他肯定得唠叨死我
and if I'm not there, I'm never gonna hear the end of it.
等等 你知道我需要什么吗 我需要可卡因
Wait! You know what I need? I need coke!
它能帮助我保持清醒
It'll keep me awake.
没错 你他妈就需要这个
Yeah, that's what you fuckin'need.
还有 能借你车用用吗
Also...can I borrow your car?
绝对他妈的不行
Absolutely fuckin' not.
我37岁
♪ I'm 37 ♪
为嗑嗨感到无比羞愧
♪And so ashamed of getting high ♪
你可以的 你可以的 宝贝
You got this. You got this, baby.
你可以的
You got this.
警车一路呼啸
♪ Squad cars screaming down the block ♪
你可以的
You got this!
拜托 宝贝
Come on, baby!
婊子 你是碧昂丝
Bitch, you Beyonce!
无可信仰
♪ Nothing to believe in ♪
警察 我们有搜查令
Police, search warrant!
举起手来
Get your hands up!
Hands up!
操
Fucker!
雷 举起手来 混蛋
Ray! Put your hands up, motherfucker!
举起手来
Put'em up!
手放背后 快
Hands behind your back, now!
趴下 趴下
Down, down!
立刻趴下
- Down, now!
不要反抗
Stop resisting!
乔治·帕西斯
George Patsis,
我是马萨诸塞州警警探雷·阿布鲁佐
I'm Sergeant Ray Abruzzo of the Massachusetts State Police.
你他妈是说马萨诸塞吗
Did you say fuckin' Massachusetts?
你所说的任何话可能会成为
Anything you say can and will be used against you
呈堂证供 兄弟
- in the court of law, pal. -
操
Fuck!
今天早些时候 马萨诸塞州警
Early this morning, the Mass State Police,
联合烟酒火器管理局和国税局
in conjunction with the ATF and the IRS,
执行了对纽约市
executed a search warrant at the home
乔治·帕西斯先生家的搜查令
of Mr. George Patsis of New York.
没错 是马萨诸塞州州警 傻逼
Yeah, that's Mass State Police, bitch.
缉毒局见鬼去吧
Suck it, DEA.
我们认为帕西斯先生
We believe that Mr. Patsis was the head
是全国最大的芬太尼和卡芬太尼
of one of the largest fentanyl and carfentanyl rings
贩毒团伙的头子 我们想要感谢合作伙伴
in the country, and we'd like to thank our partners.
这人被抓的时候还穿着内衣
Hey, hey, this guy was in his tighty- whities
在洗衣房试图毁掉一个加密笔记本电脑呢
in the Iaundry room trying to destroy an encrypted laptop.
我们抓到他了 知道他在中国搞的什么事
We got him. We got all his China shit.
-我们抓到你了 傻逼  -操你妈
We got you, motherfuckerl- Fuck you.
-抓到你了 傻逼  -没错
Got you, motherfucker. - Yeah!
能聊两句吗 警探
A word, Sergeant?
听着 我知道你要说什么
Look, I know what you're gonna say.
我没有层层上报
I broke the chain of command.
我太冲动了
And I got impulse issues.
不
No.
我是想说 你是个有毒的混账
I was gonna say you're a toxic asshole
觉得就自己全世界最行
who thinks your shit don't stink.
-行吧  -但谁管我怎么想呢
Okay. But who cares what I think.
你给我们拿下了一个案子 现在上级
You got us a win, and now the colonel has got a twinkle
赏识雷·阿布鲁佐了
in his eye for Ray Abruzzo.
他要我们跟联调局再合作一个长期案子
He wants us to head up another long- range case with the Feds,
还有烟酒火器管理局的主管特别探员
and our special agent in charge over at ATF
有个想用的卧底
has someone he wants to use as an undercover.
好 目标是谁
AII right, who's the target?
那取决于我们 但我在考虑伊曼纽尔·德尔加多
That's up to us, but I was thinking Emmanuel Delgado.
但奥西托 他很聪明 也很多疑
Yeah, but Osito he's smart and paranoid,
所以我不推荐直接对他下手
so I wouldn't recommend going directly at him.
肖恩·弗劳利怎么样
What about Shane Frawley?
我确实听到消息 他是在鳕鱼角
I did hear he was on the Cape now.
而且他侄子欧文是贩毒的
And his nephew Owen's in the drug game.
我是说那
Imean, that
那就是你抓奥西托的门路
that's your back door to Osito.
你去想个作战计划
Come up with an ops plan.
我去把卧底叫来
I'll have the undercover come in.
奎瓦斯 有人来见你
Cuevas, you got a visitor.
你很失望
You're disappointed...
因为我和照片里长得不一样 我知道
because I don't look like my pictures- - I knew it.
我很兴奋 因为你和照片里一模一样
I'm ecstatic because you look exactly like your pictures.
我都不敢相信 你终于给我打电话了
I can't believe you finally called me.
自从我在报纸上看到你的照片
I've dreamt about this
就一直想象着这一刻
since the first time I saw your picture in the paper.
那失望的肯定是你了
Then it must be you who's disappointed.
看到我在这里头 穿成这样
Seeing me in here, dressed like this.
不 完全没有
No, not at all.
你很完美
You're perfect.
所以 我有点紧张
So, um, I'm a little nervous.
你想聊什么
What would you like to talk about?
给我看你的胸
Show me your tits.
什么
What?
你听到了
You heard me.
不 不要看他们
No, don't look at them.
看着我
Look at me.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我 我从来没做过这种事
I've- I've never done anything like that.
嘘 嘘
- Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
我没让你说话
I didn't tell you to speak.
碰你自己私处
I want you to touch your pussy.
我的天
Oh. Oh, my God.
我的天 我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天
Oh, my God.
你是个好女孩 瑞秋
You're a good girl, Rachel.
喂 不能身体接触
Hey! No contact.
很快 我会让你帮我做点事情
Soon I'm going to ask you to do some things for me.
好吗
Is that okay?
好
Yeah.
特里西娅
Tricia?
嗨 是我 蕾妮
Hi, it's Renee.
我知道我们很久没联系了
Yeah, I know it's been forever.
总之
Um, anyway, uh,
我想问一下 场子能不能借我用一下很快
I was hoping you could fit me in for a quick blowout?
好
Okay.
我的天 谢谢你
Oh, my God, thank you.
好 我去换个衣服
Okay, I'll just throw on some clothes,
20分钟就到
and Il be there in 20.
好 谢了
Okay, thanks.
谢谢你 豪尔赫
Thank you, Jorge.
真他妈完蛋
Shit's all fucked up.
我们只剩大概两天的货了
We only got about two days of product left.
我们得赶紧找新货源
We need to find a new plug fast.
这肯定不容易
That won't be easy.
所以这才叫努力做事
That's why they call it work.
他们在福尔布鲁克找到了我的车
They found my car in Fall Brook.
老天 那地方有够烂的
Jesus, that place is a shithole.
我知道 是吧
I know, right?
就不能把车扔在鳕鱼角吗
Couldn't they have dumped it somewhere on the Cape at least?
你介意我出去一下吗
Uh, you mind if I take off?
没事 你去吧
Nah, not at all. Get out of here.
奎尼奥内斯 回来一下
Quinones, come back for a second.
今天你表现真的很好
That was a really good job today.
谢谢
Thanks.
阿布鲁佐警探
Sergeant Abruzzo.
-怎么了  -我是莎拉·基根
Yeah? - I'm Sarah Keegan.
我被分配来这个组负责一次卧底
I was assigned to the unit on a UC case.
他们让我找你报到
I was told to report to you.
对
Yep.
请坐
Sit down.
所以
So.
你之前干过卧底吗
you ever worked undercover before?
我刚出警校
I just got out of the academy.
六月刚毕业
Graduated in June.
是 你很年轻
Yeah, you're young.
我以为会是
And, uh, I was expecting someone
更有经验的人
with a little more experience.
你需要知道 我叔叔是烟草火器管理局的主管特别探员
KEEGAN You should know my uncle is the SAC over at ATF.
是他联系了史密斯警监 让他安排我的
KEE He called Lieutenant Smith to have me placed.
那可是这次调查里
You know that's like my boss's boss
我上级的上级
on this investigation.
挺 这挺好
That's...that's good to know.
我知道这很奇怪 但听着 我是班里第一名毕业的
I know it's weird, but, look, I graduated top of my class.
我这辈子都在跟警察打交道
I've been around cops my whole life, and.
而且 我绝对很擅长这个
for what it's worth, I'm gonna be awesome at this.
你肯定是
I'm sure you are.
明夫就开始行吗 好
Do you want to start tomorrow? Great.
还有 我不知道你知不知道这件事
And I don't know if you know this,
但我们今早刚在纽约抓了条大鱼
but we just made a major arrest this morning down in New York.
我做好准备的
I did my homework.
你的事我全都知道 阿布鲁佐警探
I know all about you, Sergeant Abruzzo.
好 挺好
Oh, okay. Good.
那挺好
That's good. Um...
欢迎加入这个组
welcome to the team.
好极了 我很兴奋
Amazing. So excited.
我是奎尼奥内斯探员
I'm Agent Quinones.
是你打电话找我说车的事
You called me about the car.
车在这儿 但我得提醒你
It's here, but I got to warn you,
It's here, but Igot to warn you,
偷车的人开得特别狠
she was rode hard and put away wet.
我真是操了
Fuck me.
我觉得大概是有瘾君子睡你车上了
Way I figure, some crackhead probably lived in here
直到他们用完了汽油
till they ran out of gas.
你最好看看还有没有油开回家
You better check you have enough to get home.
没了
Nope.
我车后备箱里有一桶应急的
I got a can in my trunk for emergencies.
-我去拿  -谢了
- Let me grab it. Thanks.
老天
Jesus.
拜托
Ugh, come on.
给
Here you go.
这应该就够了
This ought to do ya.